<list>
	<member>
		<name>Erick Rodriguez</name> 
		<role>President</role>
		<phone>828-738-6765</phone> 
		<email>erick4rodriguez@gmail.com</email>
		<bio>“Erick is a junior studying business management &amp; information systems; whose hobbies involve cooking, traveling, and being what he calls a gym rat. His background involves becoming an Eagle Scout at the age of 13, being a University Co-Instructor lecturing a semester long 2.5 hour class called Warrington Welcome, being hand selected to compete in StartupBus North America one of the most intense entrepreneurship competitions in the US where you pitch in front of gurus like Guy Kawasaki and the CTO of Marc Cuban. More recently I attended Undergraduate symposiums at University of Pennsylvania, and Google’s Mountain View headquarters; but my true entrepreneurial background comes from ecommerce where I have done a little over 6 figures in revenue.”</bio>
		<pic>images/erick.jpg</pic>
	</member>

	<member>
		<name>David Nassau</name>
		<role>President</role>
		<phone>954-643-4447</phone>
		<email>David@mshopscotch.org</email>
		<bio>“David was eClub president over the summer; he runs a non profit called “Hopping 4 a Cure” where he’s raised over $30,000 for multiple sclerosis by hosting hopscotch tournaments, was an Entrepreneurship Instructor at the Cade Museum and is currently he’s taking it easy interning for Disney World.”</bio>
		<pic>images/david.jpg</pic>
	</member>

	<member>
		<name>Aniruddh Ravindran</name>
		<role>Executive Vice President</role>
		<phone>352-871-6023</phone>
		<email>aniruddhravindran@gmail.com</email>
		<bio>“Aniruddh is doing his masters in Biomedical Engineering, and is on the verge of publishing two papers after a year of comprehensive research. In the past he’s played soccer for the Indian National team, has raised loads of money for noble causes in his undergraduate years, and is currently part of two startup companies; one of which placed 2nd in Startup Weekend Gainesville last year. Moreover, Aniruddh here similar to Giovanni placed top 16 in the $40,000 bus plan competition among 147 original team members. And when he’s not doing all of this he’s salsa dancing”</bio>
		<pic>images/ani.jpg</pic>
	</member>

	<member>
		<name>Kevin Prescott</name>
		<role>Director of Marketing</role>
		<phone>703-314-2695</phone>
		<email>kpres27@gmail.com</email>
		<bio>“Kevin is a junior at the University of Florida, double majoring in both Business Management and Telecommunication Production. Currently he is the Director of Marketing and is also the Chief Video Man for CRU. One day Kevin desires to open his own restaurant while doing production on the side. During his free time, Kevin loves to play Assassins Creed and watch lacrosse.</bio>
		<pic>images/kevin.jpg</pic>
	</member>

	<member>
		<name>Jerry Declasse</name>
		<role>Director of Marketing</role>
		<phone>813-361-9810</phone>
		<email>jerrydeclasse@gmail.com</email>
		<bio>Jerry Declasse is a third year Business/Psych double major and is also in the Innovation Academy program. He is very involved in the Gainesville entrepreneurial community and has worked with companies such as Feathr, FreshSpark, as well as many companies in incubators such as StarterSpace and The Innovation Hub. As a digital marketing specialist, Jerry has built online presences and product launches that have reached millions of people. He is also a big fan of fedoras.</bio>
		<pic>images/jerry.jpg</pic>
	</member>

	<member>
		<name>Karin Ulloa</name>
		<role>Director of Marketing</role>
		<phone>813-418-2835</phone>
		<email>karinulloa@hotmail.com</email>
		<bio>“Karin is a junior marketing major with a minor in accounting and entrepreneurship from Lima, Peru. Upon graduating she would like to be a marketing consultant, recently she has studied in Beijing, China. Interned with Aramark; and been involved with numerous organizations such as Adopted Gators, and Navigators International”</bio>
		<pic>images/karin.jpg</pic>
	</member>

	<member>
		<name>Giovanni Crimi</name>
		<role>VP of University Outreach</role>
		<phone>954-439-6922</phone>
		<email>giocrimi@yahoo.com</email>
		<bio>“Gio is studying finance and info systems, is a brother in Delta Sigma Pi; and recently placed top 16 in the $40,000 UF Big Idea Bus. Plan Competition for his startup App that utilizes augmented reality and trading cards; which forced him to become a self taught learner of SQL, PHP, HTML, and CSS”</bio> 
		<pic>images/gio.jpg</pic>
	</member>
	 
	<member>
		<name>James Ziv</name>
		<role>Innovation Academy Ambassador</role>
		<phone>786-351-7118</phone>
		<email>Ajsfinance@aol.com</email>
		<bio>“James is a sophomore Innovation Academy student majoring in Finance with a minor in Philosophy. James recently was a tenant at the local incubator the Center for Innovation &amp; Economic Development working on a mobile carpooling app. He’s been involved in the Servant Leadership program, has been a finalist in the Enactus Ethics Case competition and has served as Finance director of the Student Investment Club where he manages a clientele of local sponsors”</bio>
		<pic>images/james.jpg</pic>
	</member>

	<member>
		<name>Andrew Birkett</name>
		<role>VP of Industry Outreach</role>
		<phone>407-222-7814</phone>
		<email>Andrew.r.birkett@gmail.com</email>
		<bio>“Andrew loves cars, and has a 1979 Camaro Z28, his hobbies involve photography; and currently he’s working on creating a line of trading cards for sports cars”</bio>
		<pic>images/andrew.jpg</pic>
	</member>

	<member>
		<name>Dylan Schreiner</name>
		<role>Secretary</role>
		<phone>904-655-2613</phone>
		<email>dylanschreiner1@gmail.com</email>
		<bio>“Dylan loves traveling and entrepreneurship; growing up he lived all across the country, moving frequently. He’s visited four continents and his goal is to visit all 7; his goal is to conquer public speaking and is part of a local toastmaster club. Currently he’s interning for Onminox Publishing, and interactive textbook publisher in the Innovation Hub”</bio>
		<pic>images/dylan.jpg</pic>
	</member>

	<member>
		<name>Jason Hong</name>
		<role>VP of Finance/Fundraising</role>
		<phone>904-403-0221</phone>
		<email>jasonarigatou@ufl.edu</email>
		<bio>“Jason is a senior Finance major with accounting and entrepreneurship minors. Last semester he did a study abroad in London while simultaneously doing an internship; his hobbies involve cooking, and working with sculptures”</bio>
		<pic>images/jason.jpg</pic>
	</member>
	 
	<member>
		<name>Nick Tardif</name>
		<role>VP of Technology</role>
		<phone>727-580-5971</phone>
		<email>nicktardif@gmail.com</email>
		<bio>“Nick loves to program and is heavily involved with UF’s Software Development community. Last year he worked with the Gainesville based startup Neuronet Learning, where he developed an educational motion tracking game for children. More recently he interned with Amazon in Seattle, developing features for the Kindle and in his spare time he enjoys hammocks, traveling, camping, and hiking”</bio>
		<pic>images/nick.jpg</pic>
	</member>

	<member>
		<name>Piyush Gupta</name>
		<role>VP of Technology</role>
		<phone>510-456-8990</phone>
		<email>gupta.piyush@live.com</email>
		<bio>-No Bio Yet-</bio>
		<pic>images/piyush.jpg</pic>
	</member>

	<member>
		<name>Jenel Schwind</name>
		<role>VP of Social</role>
		<phone>941-539-6511</phone>
		<email>jschwind@ufl.edu</email>
		<bio>“Jenel is an active piano player and has been playing for 11 years now, she loves math and considers herself a life time member of Mu Alpha Thera. More recently she has been learning website development, excel, and other software’s; currently she is a host and administrative assistant at Bonefish grille.”</bio>
		<pic>images/jenel.jpg</pic>
	</member>
</list>
