<list>
    <member>
        <name>Erick Rodriguez</name>
        <role>Co-President</role>
        <phone>828-738-6765</phone>
        <email>erick4rodriguez@gmail.com</email>
        <bio>Erick is a junior studying business management &amp; information systems. His hobbies involve cooking, traveling, and being a “gym rat”. He became Eagle Scout at 13, was a UF Co-Instructor, was hand selected to compete in StartupBus North America (one of the most intense entrepreneurship competitions in North America); and will be doing an internship with Google this summer.</bio>
        <pic>images/erick.jpg</pic>
    </member>
    <member>
        <name>David Nassau</name>
        <role>Co-President</role>
        <phone>954-643-4447</phone>
        <email>David@mshopscotch.org</email>
        <bio>David is founder and president of a non-profit called Hopping 4 a Cure where he’s raised over $35,000 for Multiple Sclerosis by hosting hopscotch tournaments. David was an entrepreneurship instructor at the CadeMuseum last semester; just recently returned from a Disney internship in Orlando; and is a part time triathlete.</bio>
        <pic>images/david.jpg</pic>
    </member>
    <member>
        <name>Aniruddh Ravindran</name>
        <role>Executive Vice President</role>
        <phone>352-871-6023</phone>
        <email>aniruddhravindran@gmail.com</email>
        <bio>Aniruddh is doing his masters in Biomedical Engineering, and is on the verge of publishing two papers. He used to play soccer for the India National team, has raised large sums of money for non-profits in his undergrad years; and is currently a part of two startups. And when he’s not doing all of the above you can find him salsa dancing in the evenings.</bio>
        <pic>images/ani.jpg</pic>
    </member>
    <member>
        <name>Giovanni Crimi</name>
        <role>Vice President of Events</role>
        <phone>954-439-6922</phone>
        <email>giocrimi@yahoo.com</email>
        <bio>Giovanni is studying finance and information systems, and is a brother in Delta Sigma Pi (a professional business fraternity). Last year, Giovanni placed top 16 in UF’s $40,000 Big Idea business plan competition for his startup app that utilizes augmented reality and trading cards; resulting in him becoming a self taught learner of SQL, PHP, HTML, and CSS.</bio>
        <pic>images/giov.jpg</pic>
    </member>
    <member>
        <name>James Ziv</name>
        <role>Vice President of Outreach</role>
        <phone>786-351-7118</phone>
        <email>Ajsfinance@aol.com</email>
        <bio>James is a sophomore Innovation Academy student majoring in Finance with a minor in Philosophy. He was a tenant at a local incubator (Center for Innovation &amp; Economic Development) where he was working on an app to revolutionize the carpooling industry. More recently he was a finalist in the Enactus Ethics Case competition, and on the side James serves as Director of Finance for Student Investment Club.</bio>
        <pic>images/james.jpg</pic>
    </member>
    <member>
        <name>James Cherry</name>
        <role>Vice President of Marketing</role>
        <phone>904-562-9159</phone>
        <email>jamescherry93@gmail.com</email>
        <bio>James is a 3rd year Mathematics Major with interests in anthropology, biology and literature. He’s president of American Marketing Association while simultaneously maintaining involvement in Accent’s Speaker's Bureau, Action SG, Leadership Development Cabinet, Student Government Finance, Gator Innovators, and UF Housing. Moreover, James currently works as Director of Marketing at the Gainesville-based mobile app startup Bafit LLC and is a College Marketing Representative for Ubisoft.</bio>
        <pic>images/cherry.jpg</pic>
    </member>
    <member>
        <name>Vera Toncheva</name>
        <role>Events Director</role>
        <phone>352-219-1158</phone>
        <email>vtoncheva@ufl.edu</email>
        <bio>Vera is currently a Masters in Entrepreneurship Student. She has always been involved in student-run NGOs and is proud to have served at the executive board of ABLE – the Association of Bulgarian Leaders and Entrepreneurs. Currently, she is working on a startup and is prospecting additional entrepreneurial opportunities. Aside from that, she loves art, dance, photography and her biggest passion is traveling.</bio>
        <pic>images/vera.jpg</pic>
    </member>
    <member>
        <name>Maria Vargas</name>
        <role>Events Director</role>
        <phone>352-278-7319</phone>
        <email>iavargas@ufl.edu</email>
        <bio>Maria is a freshmen Business Admin and IA student. In 2012 she co-founded Mind Your Own Business (MYOB) to promote entrepreneurship. MYOB has placed 1st in state competitions, as well as 2nd in international competitions. Maria is currently a sales associate at Cymplify, and a student assistant in the UF Social Entrepreneurship Initiative and Fellowship program. Maria loves being involved with the community and bringing people together to do positive things.</bio>
        <pic>images/maria.jpg</pic>
    </member>
    <member>
        <name>Nick Tardif</name>
        <role>Technology Director</role>
        <phone>727-580-5971</phone>
        <email>ntardif@ufl.edu</email>
        <bio>Nick loves to program and is heavily involved with UF’s Software Development community. Last year he developed an educational motion tracking game for NeuroNet Learning and also interned for Amazon working on Kindle software. Now he is the lead developer at peerfit, a flexible gym class membership company. In his spare time he enjoys hammocks, traveling, camping, and hiking.</bio>
        <pic>images/nick.jpg</pic>
    </member>
    <member>
        <name>Andrew Birkett</name>
        <role>Photographer</role>
        <phone>407-222-7814</phone>
        <email>Andrew.r.birkett@gmail.com</email>
        <bio>Andrew is a sophomore currently working on two startups; a photography business and a trading card line involving sports cars. Andrew owns a 1979 Camaro Z28, and LOVES cars (talk “cars” to him and he’ll talk your ear off). In his free time he enjoys going to car shows, while practicing photography.</bio>
        <pic>images/andrew.jpg</pic>
    </member>
    <member>
        <name>Tyler McGrath</name>
        <role>University Outreach Director</role>
        <phone>561-628-2285</phone>
        <email>tylerm9914@yahoo.com</email>
        <bio>Tyler is a freshmen Management major minoring in entrepreneurship. His hobbies involve running, fishing, and overall consuming the “fresh air” of the outdoors. This past summer he worked with his Father’s startup company installing IT systems; and he hopes to help his father grow the business through his experiences with school and Entrepreneurship Club. Moreover, he is currently interning for a moving company in Gainesville.</bio>
        <pic>images/tyler.jpg</pic>
    </member>
    <member>
        <name>Chuck Call</name>
        <role>Industry Outreach Director</role>
        <phone>863-370-5352</phone>
        <email>ccall@ufl.edu</email>
        <bio>Chuck is a returning student completing his Bachelor's Degree in Business Administration. Like other conventional students he studies full time. He is a husband and father of 3.  He relocated his family to Gainesville 6 months ago to finish his degree at UF. Chuck plans to graduate with a new career in place, and he thinks Entrepreneurship Club will provide a unique and well rounded experience, to “kick-off” his new career trajectory.</bio>
        <pic>images/chuck.jpg</pic>
    </member>
    <member>
        <name>Clint Ferguson</name>
        <role>Recruitment Director</role>
        <phone>561-634-0502</phone>
        <email>clintdferguson@ufl.edu</email>
        <bio>Clint has a robust passion for startups; he has worked for several companies including having interned for SeaWorld. He took 2nd in 2013 Startup Weekend, as well as top 16 in the 2013 Big Idea Competition. Clint also runs a successful YouTube channel with 15,000 subscribers, with his most watched video having received over 100,000 views. Clint is president of Minecraft club; and is currently working on installing a fountain show at the Reitz. </bio>
        <pic>images/clint.jpg</pic>
    </member>
    <member>
        <name>Rachael Tonietto</name>
        <role>Online Promotions Director</role>
        <phone>954-376-9009</phone>
        <email>rachaeltonietto@ufl.edu</email>
        <bio>Rachael is currently a marketing major minoring in entrepreneurship and retail. She enjoys running, drawing and overall staying active. She is alumna of Women of Tomorrow and plans to pay it forward in the future serving as a mentor for the program to help the next generation of women reach their goals. Rachael has been involved in a nationwide fundraiser for homeless teenagers for 2 years now; and hopes to make a similar impact in Gainesville.</bio>
        <pic>images/rachael.jpg</pic>
    </member>
    <member>
        <name>Angelinga Ferris</name>
        <role>Social Director</role>
        <phone>802-917-1599</phone>
        <email>angelinaferris@ymail.com</email>
        <bio>Angelina is 3rd year Finance major. She is currently a teaching assistance for Principles of Entrepreneurship class, as well as a sister in Delta Zeta sorority. Last year she was honorably inducted into the National Association of Professional Women; and in her spare time she enjoys, traveling, reading, and cooking Mediterranean style food.</bio>
        <pic>images/angelina.jpg</pic>
    </member>
</list>

